

Abubakkar Sajid

Web developer

About Me

I'm a Frontend Developer with 1 year of experience, specializing in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React to build responsive, user-friendly websites. Passionate about creating clean, efficient code and continuously learning new technologies to enhance user experiences.

Contact

- **(** +92 3241851476
- abubakkarsajid4@gmail.com
- chungi amar sidhu

ঞ্জি Skills

- Web Design
- Web developements
- Frontend Developer

Education

- (2020-2022)

 MATRIC(SCIENCE)
- (2022-2024)
 INTER (COMPUTER SCIENCE)
 KIPs college
- (2024 -)
 BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE
 Lahore Leads university

Experience

- (2022 -2023)

 JALSONIC NETWORKS

 WEB DEVELOPEMENT(FRONTEND)
- (2023 -2024)
 ONESTBIRD
 WEB DEVELOPER
 (FRONTEND DEVELOPER)

At Language

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React-js